Victor Antonio Balbuena Bello

Morelos, Mexico |
 | <u>balbuenabellovictorantonio@gmail.com</u> |
 | +52 734 115 6483

in LinkedIn |
Portfolio |
GitHub

Skills:

Javascript | Typescript | C# | .NET | MSSQL | MYSQL | Angular | React | Redux | SASS | Tailwind | Bootstrap GIT | Entity Framework | Frontend | Backend | English | Spanish

Profile:

Web developer with more than 2 years of experience developing with frontend and backend technologies with extensive experience in quality software development. Graduated from Computer Systems Engineering with a specialty in web and mobile applications in 2021 with experience in remote modality and work on site.

Work Experience:

Full Stack Web Developer - Process Ecology Inc, Alberta, Canadá (Remote)

August 2021 - April 2023

I worked as a full stack web developer with Angular and Net Core developing projects, creating interface components, API consumption, requirements implementation, layout and communication between services.

- Frontend development with Angular (Typescript) creating components, RxJS, Directives, and more.
- Create fully responsive views following the layouts proposed by the design team.
- Backend development with Net Core (C#) creating web api services, working with the code-first methodology.

Technologies: Angular 10+, Typescript, C#, Entity Framework Core, GIT, MSSQL, RxJS, NgRx.

Frontend Web Developer - CCG UNAM - Morelos, Mexico

February 2021 - June 2021

I worked as a Frontend web developer developing projects, creating components, consumption of API's, implementation of requirements.

- Frontend development with React (Javascript) creating components, Hooks, State, Fetch API, Axios.
- Create fully responsive views following the layouts proposed by the design team.
- Project structuring planning.

Technologies: React, JavaScript, GIT, Axios, Fetch API.

Soft skills:

Communication, resilience, teamwork, self-taught, perseverance.

Education:

Instituto Tecnológico de Zacatepec - Morelos, Mexico

Computer Systems Engineer August 2016 - July 2021

Languages:

Spanish: Native proficiency English: B2 Upper Intermediate